

# CONNOR READNOUR

7425 S LAND PARK DR. APT 75 SACRAMENTO CA, 95831

#### **SUMMARY**

Dedicated information technology professional with over 5 years of experience working with highly collaborative teams using a diverse set of computer software & languages, including: Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, AutoCAD, Revit, SQL Queries & SQL Server 2008-2016.

## **SKILLS**

- Bootstrap, jQuery
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Responsive Design
- AutoCAD, Revit
- SQL, SQL Server
- Excel, Word, PowerPoint
- ARCHIBUS Web Central
- RSC SpaceView
- UX/UI Testing
- Lifecycle testing
- Data Analysis
- Agile Development
- Report Creation
- Jira, Slack, GoToMeeting
- Microsoft Outlook
- Chrome Dev Tools

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER | CAD DESIGNER | IWMS ADMIN ROBERT STEPHEN CONSULTING

AUGUST 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2020

- Developed over 25 responsive Bootstrap webpages with 100+ design updates using HTML5, CSS3, and jQuery/JavaScript.
- Polylined 100,000 150,000 sq. feet per week in AutoCAD, while cataloging custom room standards and types.
- Customized several hundred tasks, reports and home pages in ARCHIBUS Web Central.
- Created numerous Excel direct connect reports and designed Crystal Reports to give actionable insights into customer data.

#### **TESTING ANALYST | DATA ANALYST** APPLIED SYSTEMS

AUGUST 2015 - JULY 2018

August 2015

GPA: 3.3 / 4.0

- Identified and tested thousands of defects in ETL software during initial, regression, and release testing utilizing SQL queries.
- Imported, exported and manipulated large data sets in multi-million row databases under tight deadlines.
- Generated production databases using our ETL tools and wrote release notes for all assigned user stories.
- Managed client conversions to Applied Systems EPIC from various source systems including TAM, INSTAR and VISION.

## **EDUCATION**

**B.S. in Operations Management & Information Systems Northern Illinois University** 







